I, Maria Annovazzi, also known as Mimi,
was raised to be my family's heir
until my younger brother was born
and I was freed from that responsibility.
However, despite reaching marriageable
age, I still haven't found a partner,
so I reached out to my distant
relatives in the Ametis family
to study abroad in
the Kingdom of Rubini, but...
I, Renato di Rubini, first prince
of the Kingdom of Rubini,
hereby call off our engagement.
The first thing you should do is...
buy some glasses!
Your Grace!
Father!
Are you all right?
Someone call a doctor!
Your Grace!
Always a Catch!
Episode 2
How I Caught the One That Got Away
That was some party.
I'm terribly sorry.
As Prince Renato's aide,
I offer my deepest apologies.
Duke Ametis has been sent home
with the royal physician.
I'm so sorry for hurting you both.
You don't have to apologize so much.
Your Highness!
Brother!
I-I am terribly sorry
about what happened.
If you're sorry, then
that's good enough for me.
No, please let us offer
an official apology at a later date.
I have no idea what's going on anymore.
Don't say that. Prince Renato
really is sorry for what he did.
Besides...
This incident could postpone him
being made crown prince.
Are you okay, Aida?
Weren't you supposed to officially
announce your engagement today?
Prince Renato never wanted to get
engaged to me in the first place.
What?
To be honest, I was expecting him
to call it off eventually.
So don't worry about it.
He didn't want to?
That's still not a reason to have
that conversation at that party.
BONK BONK BONK
And you never bullied Eleonora
or whatever her name is.
I know better than anyone
that you'd never do that.
And who confuses another
girl for his fiancée?
We hardly ever saw each other.
So he doesn't remember what
you look like? Unbelievable.
But Mimi...
Don't blame Prince Renato too much.
He's a very intelligent
and thoughtful person.
Intelligent?
I won't if you don't want me to.
Thank you.
Anyway, I'm more worried about you.
Me?
You attracted a lot of odd attention.
I hope it won't interfere
with finding a promising catch.
That's Right
That's right. I'm here to find a spouse
because I got no attention back home.
Not only that, but I was dumped when
I was never engaged to begin with.
What a disgrace.
I've become a terrible and honorless
lady. The worst of the worst.
I don't think people would go that far.
Oh, no. I spoke my mind again.
I'm sure Prince Renato
will correct the situation.
I plan to clear up any confusion as well.
Thank you.
Seriously, that stupid prince
ruined everything.
All women look the same to me
All women look the same to me.
The next time I see him,
I'm going to beat him up.
Sorry!
Don't do that.
But compared to Prince Renato,
Prince Placido is a nice person.
He talked to me before
when I was all by myself,
and he apologized profusely today
even though he wasn't at fault.
You're right.
You and Prince Placido are close, right?
It's more that we're childhood friends
who have known each other for a long time.
Really? I think you two
would make a great couple.
Does Aida have feelings
for Prince Placido?
Wait. That would mean the shit prince—
I mean, Prince Renato calling off
their engagement is a good thing?
But won't that harm Aida's reputation?
But if they call off their engagement
being called off, then...
Uh, she be engaged
to Prince Renato, and...
Forget it. I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
My apologies.
Please wait here a while longer.
Prince Renato should arrive
as soon as he's finished.
I can't believe he
actually invited me here.
Anyway, this is definitely
a castle drawing room.
It's as luxurious as a palace.
The fragrant butter...
The refined sweetness of the cream...
Their private pâtissier
must be top notch, too.
Forgive me for keeping you
waiting, Lady Annovazzi.
SMILE
Not at all.
He remembered my name properly.
Most people get it wrong.
Do you mind if I sit?
Go ahead.
Seriously? He's genuinely
attempting to apologize.
I'm truly sorry for what I did.
Placido told me why
you're studying abroad.
I sincerely regret tarnishing
your honor and background.
If that's how you feel,
introduce me to a promising catch.
A promising catch? I'll think about it.
I spoke my mind again.
Don't worry about it, Lady Annovazzi.
I-I'm sorry.
Annovazzi isn't easy to pronounce, is it?
You can call me Maria, or even
Mimi if that would be easier.
Thank you, Lady Maria.
Lady Aida may have told you already,
but I've been avoiding her.
Yes.
I've been having Placido escort her
while I've hardly seen her.
So I didn't even know what
Lady Aida currently looks like.
But why do you need to avoid her so much?
I heard you were childhood friends.
Yes, so I knew her hair color.
That's why I was certain you were her.
Few people have such
beautiful golden hair.
Th-Thank you.
But why did you do that
in the first place?
That was a public setting and your
graduation party. A celebration.
If you're so intelligent, you
must've known what would happen.
You may not become crown prince anymore.
Did you not consider that?
I thought everything would go well
if I didn't become crown prince.
What?
Now that you've said that,
tell me the details.
I won't tell anyone.
Well, depending on
what you say, of course.
Oh, sheesh.
Come on. Whisper it to me.
I'm not from this kingdom,
and I'll be gone eventually.
Feel like telling me now?
The truth is...
Placido is in love with Lady Aida.
What?
Wait, does that mean Aida and
Prince Placido love each other?
Should I tell Prince Renato?
No, it's Aida's secret.
Oh, but...
Don't tell anyone, please.
He's easy to read. He's loved her
since we were children.
But Lady Aida's father is set on having
his daughter marry the crown prince.
Oh...
So if I don't become crown prince,
it will be Placido, the second son.
Then everything will work out
nicely, or so I thought.
What? This guy's actually really nice.
But I made a critical error.
I even dragged someone into this mess
who had nothing to do with it.
Your Highness, you want to
make it up to me, right?
Yes, of course.
Then don't worry about
the promising catch.
Treat me to a delicious meal instead.
What? A delicious meal?
DUMBFOUNDED...
What did you just think of?
Steaks at Malvar's.
GLOW
Steak! That sounds wonderful!
Let's go eat our fill!
And fix your lack of sleep
by the time we get steaks.
You have bags under your eyes.
You're right. I'm busy, but I often
have trouble sleeping as well.
I can fall asleep in three seconds.
I'm jealous.
Then as a treat...
I'll teach you the Annovazzi
family counting song.
One!
Two! Three! Four!
Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine!
Ten!
DUMBFOUNDED...
Remember what I just did
before you go to sleep.
What?
Whenever I do it for my baby brother,
he laughs and sleeps soundly.
I'm sure it'll help you sleep, too.
Your baby brother?
Yes. He turns four this year.
His name is Teodorico.
Y-You're treating me
like your baby brother?
Teo likes this, too.
SWIPE
And this.
How about this?
Please, no more.
I-I surrender. I'm exhausted
from laughing so much.
I'm glad to hear that.
Hunger and lack of sleep
are enemies of humankind.
Rest well, Your Highness.
I'll try.
I'll think of your face
before I go to sleep tonight.
Aida was right. He's smart.
He watches Prince Placido closely, too.
That little thief.
Always a Catch!
This looks good.
No wonder you recommended this place.
Go ahead and eat your fill.
All right. Thanks for the meal.
So good!
I'm glad you like it.
I don't know what
I would've done if you didn't.
Of course I like it.
Are you sure you're okay
with paying for this?
I don't mind splitting the bill.
Let me treat you today.
I'd like to thank you for the other day.
Thank me?
Every time I recall your
counting song, it warms my heart.
I haven't slept that soundly in a while.
What?
GULP...
That was delicious.
And I haven't had a
meal this enjoyable in ages.
The investiture ceremony
has been rescheduled, hasn't it?
Apparently, though I wouldn't
have minded being disinherited.
What?
Your Highness.
Lady Maria, forgive me,
but something's come up.
I can't escort you home, but
I've arranged for a carriage.
That's more than enough.
Worst case, I could run home.
Oh, this isn't the carriage we arrived in.
Should I tell Aida how
Prince Placido feels?
I feel bad about being
the only one treated to lunch.
But he did tell me to keep it secret.
Why is everything so difficult
when other people are involved?
Huh?
Where am I?
Get out.
You don't have to order me around.
You didn't even realize
you'd been kidnapped?
You're quite the dummy, Maria Annobaddie.
It's Annovazzi.
Prince Renato got it right.
You're so infuriating.
Inconsiderate and awful.
My sisters do often tell me
to be more ladylike.
So, do you have business with me,
Lady Eleonora Casciari?
Yes, obviously. I wouldn't
approach you if I didn't.
I was about to seduce Prince Renato, too.
But all he cares about is my father,
like who he met and where he went.
Oh, my.
As a result, his bribery were
exposed and he was arrested.
Bribery?
That's none of your business.
I see.
Prince Renato allowed you to follow
him around because he knew that.
Who's following him around?
He ignored Aida partially
for Prince Placido
and partially to glean information
from the baron's daughter.
He did it for his kingdom.
Now you listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
Stop scheming and live a decent life.
Are you stupid?
You're going to write
a letter to His Highness.
What?
If you refuse...
Wait, what am I supposed to write?
Should I thank him for the steak?
Isn't it obvious?
Ask him to help Baron Casciari and
his daughter in exchange for your life.
What?
We're taking you hostage and
fleeing across the border.
I can't do that.
Then I'll send him one of your fingers.
That's brutal.
What? Lady Maria hasn't returned yet?
No. I thought you might
know where she went.
After having lunch with her, I...
You rushed back because Baron
Casciari had begun testifying.
I shouldn't have sent her home alone.
Please don't blame yourself,
Your Highness.
Finding Lady Maria is our top priority.
Yes, you're both right.
Raimondo, prepare a horse.
I'm going back to Malvar's.
Perhaps someone in the area
saw or heard something.
Placido.
Yes, Brother.
Look after Lady Aida.
Understood.
My fingers are safe,
but what should I do now?
I guess I'll have to escape.
SNEAK
What happened? Tell me.
I was suddenly struck on the head.
Do you remember anything else?
Anything at all?
I heard the sound of a large carriage.
They said they were heading north.
North?
There's only one road loading north.
If we hurry, we could
catch up to them. Yah!
Your Highness!
Drive the carriage!
We're going after him!
Don't think you can escape.
Huh?
She's over there!
What are you doing? After her!
Stop!
She's so fast for a lady!
Have you given up?
You'd better do as we say.
No hard feelings, milady!
One!
Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Get her already!
The Annovazzi family is
a renowned family of martial artists.
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
I was raised to be the Annovazzi
family heir despite being the youngest
because I was the strongest
of all my sisters.
Ten!
Oh, no. I'm so scared.
I'm glad you're safe.
These men suddenly attacked me
and then fell down for some reason.
You handled yourself quite impressively.
Since when were you watching?
Since you brushed off Eleonora's
attempt to stop you and fled.
You saw everything! It's over!
My life as a noblewoman is over!
Take them away.
Come on, stand up.
Are you hurt?
No.
Any pain?
No, no pain.
That's good.
Um, why am I sitting in your lap?
Eleonora will be investigated
by the authorities.
She was paying bribes as well.
You're ignoring me?
That must've been quite the fright.
You poor thing.
No one's ever said that to me before.
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
I did what anyone would've done.
I see.
So, um... could you let me down now?
No.
STRUGGLE
But...
What? Why can't I push you away?
STRUGGLE
May I call you Mimi as well?
What? Yes, of course, but...
Do you recall how I told you
thinking of your face helped me sleep?
It's true.
It's been so long since I've been
able to forget the responsibilities
of the crown prince, government,
and economy to feel so calm.
I feel like the fog before
my eyes has been lifted.
You sound like you've
received a divine revelation.
Indeed, perhaps I have.
Mimi.
Marry me.
What?
Translation:
Timing:
Sho Stifler
Mariana Martinez
Editing:
Quality Control:
Alicia Ashby
Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control:     Michelle Tymon
Wh-What are you saying?
I said I'd find you a promising catch.
There is no catch more promising
than Prince Renato.
H-How long have you been there?
From the start.
No, you weren't! You totally weren't!
I was.
No, you weren't!
I didn't see you!
I was here.
But I didn't see you!
My family emphasized a clean plate
as much as martial arts,
so everyone always says, "Wow, when did
you finish your food? It's already gone!"
Do I really eat that fast?
Just the other day, Aida said...
Next Time
How I Trained to Become a Lady
Oh, I said that out loud again.